Words, music, arrangement
If you can shake it out
I'm not ashamed to say what I've done
Why do girls only remember makeup, they don't care about me
I'm protected, and over time, I start looking for a way to fight
Victims, they come... perpetrators of disasters...
The land of the dying, the life that breaks the shackles.
It's all the wind's fault. I can't let it destroy my dreams of being with someone else.
I'm me. I'm a little bit crazy.
I'll be official, you can try to believe the same.
Whether you cry or laugh, please, just smile
All my beautiful dreams, all my lies
All my dreams, all my dreams
Loose, loose, loose, loose, loose
If you run with your dreams, you'll sing your way to the finish line
I never get tired of the game
I wanted to win, too
The indispensable fruit of the game was competing
The rest of my fingernails are gathering
I've been swept off my feet, I've been grazed by the look-over
from the corner to the bone to the discarded
spread to a naked lady
floated somewhere
yesterday when I approached her
there is a life that lingers
there is a life that lingers on
whose fault is it
I don't care what your hobbies are
I am what I am
I have no more money than you
I'll be official
We can be just as sincere
I'll shoot and I'll guess
I can't win, I lose face
The dream of dullness
Various bodies
Let's live together
Her back is all over the place
Even if I'm holding the palm of someone else's hand
I'm still me
I'm me, I'm me, I'm me
I'll be official too
I'll just have to trust them
Whether you cry or laugh
there is nowhere to go
It's a hard dream
Let go of the lies
Let's live free
You really are
You painted Welsh
I'll tell you the lie.
See you later.
Cherry Blossom
Zazagato
The Hub
Born
Prostée, this time with Kanami Ishiguri from Ocha-no-Oma and Nanami Kubota from Ocha-no-Oma!
Please stay with us until the end of the show!
Today, September 11th, is the release date of Ocha-no-Oma's fourth single "Chihayaburu Tomodachi Tenten Chizu"!
At the beginning of this article, we showed you a live video of Chihayaburu.
It makes me feel a little nostalgic, doesn't it?
That's right.
The song "Chihayaburu" was performed for the first time on the first day of the Hello Project concert this summer.
I performed it for the first time as a surprise for everyone.
I still remember how excited I was when I performed it for the first time.
This song is a song about the feelings of a very cool, strong and beautiful woman.
The dance performance with a great sense of style is the highlight of the show, so I hope you all enjoy it.
The other song, "Friend Tentai Zu" is a bright and cheerful song in contrast to "Chahamblee".
The lyrics of this song are very sympathetic to me.
I got the impression that everyone said they could really relate to the lyrics.
I also love to hang out with my friends, which is something I cherish.
There are a lot of lyrics in this song that I can really relate to.
I hope that everyone will take a look at the lyrics and listen to the song.
At the end of the song, there is a part where everyone can sing "la-la-la-la" together.
I hope everyone can enjoy it together!
I hope you can enjoy it with me!
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go.
We're going to start with a taiko performance, and I'm going to show you what I did last year.
I'm wearing my yukata on my feet, but I've prepared a more powerful presentation.
I've prepared a more powerful presentation.
I'm going to do my best to give a performance that is as cool as I am full of myself.
I did my best on the taiko last year, but I'm not as good as I was last year, and I'm not as good as I was last year.
There will be a lot of kaku-uchi (corner drummers).
There are some parts that are burped.
I can do that really well.
And there are also solos.
We didn't have that last time.
I'm getting nervous.
So I'm going to do my best to do the solo perfectly.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm nervous, but I'm going to be strong.
But you know, it's raining a little bit.
I want to do my best to make everyone's hearts sunny with our power.
This time, I'm going to perform the Idol Job Change Ondo.
I'm going to give a lecture by myself.
But I've been told that I'm free to go there.
But he was watching me.
But it's not easy.
I don't know what to do if they say I can do whatever I want.
I don't know what to do.
So don't be confused.
Don't get confused. Don't get lost.
I'm going to do my best to get it right.
This time, I'm going to play my instrument on stage from the audience's seats.
I'm really looking forward to it. I'll do my best.
Don't forget the microphone!
Bye, bye, bye.
Bye-bye!
This time, I'm going to go down to the audience seats and come up to the stage with water tempo and so on.
I want to be able to make a lot of eye contact with this person.
Please answer me, Mina-chan.
Please answer me.
Ehhhh...
Uhhh...
In three minutes.
It's okay.
Mina!
I'm not crying.
I'm not crying
Why that guy?
Third, Mizuho, Saori, Mao, Yumi, Shiori, Runo, Yu, and Fuuka.
Let's do our best to make this dreary weather fly away.
Let's do our best to put a smile on our faces, too!
Camerian!
Yay!
Everyone, calm down.
Let's do this dance.
Keep going, next time.
Keep going.
Oh, let's go.
That's why it looks like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Can we go?
You can do it. You can do it.
Here.
This is it.
I'll do my best!
Oh, my gosh!
He's so cute.
Are you here?
Here, here they are!
Oh, that's it!
I see!
I'll just be a little bit longer.
If you're here,
And I'm flying too fast.
Okay, nee!
Keep going, next time.
It's so hot, let's get some ice cream and cheer ourselves up.
This is Haloste, brought to you by tea aunts Kanami Ishiguri and Nami Kubota.
From here, we'd like to talk a little about each other.
First of all, I, Ishiguri, will ask Nami Kubota a few questions.
So let's not think too much and answer them at a quick pace.
Yes, I'm Nami Kubota.
Shall we?
I'll do my best.
Okay, I'll go.
Yes, I'll go.
What was the first thing that came to your mind when you saw the lyrics of today's single, "Friend Astronomical Chart"?
Which girl?
Kubota loves shoujo manga.
The scene where she gets bitten by a vampire.
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us ended on September 1.
Whose scene inspired you personally?
Akari Endo's sexy expression.
Who is the cutest person in the world today?
I am Curno!
Nanami Kubota.
Two years have passed since Ochanoma made its major debut.
What is the most memorable thing someone has said to you during that time?
Yes, thank you for becoming our idol!
Oh, so...
I wanted to ask you something.
Who is the cutest person in the world today? I wanted to ask you who is the cutest person in the world today.
I wanted you to answer "who is the cutest person in the world today", so I was really happy.
Yes, I am.
Yes, fans often say thank you for becoming an idol, Nanami.
There are many paths to becoming an idol, but thank you for choosing to be an idol.
I want to be an idol because I want to be an idol.
I'm really happy that you guys appreciate and support me for doing what I want to do.
I want to continue to do my best as an idol.
That's so nice.
Questions for Kanami will be asked after the VTR.
Halostage
Haloste
Ocha no oma
Chia Yaburu is now on sale
Tea Horse
Friends celestial chart now on sale
Haloste
Next I would like to ask Kanami-chan a question
Yes, I'll do my best
Yes, I'm nervous
Yes, I'll do my best.
What did you want to express most in the new single "Chihaya Blue"?
Roughness
Oh!
Ochanomama Live Tour 2024 Season 2 has started in our hometown, Japan.
How do you think it will be different from Season 1?
Bijul!
Ushal!
Yes, KANAMI-chan, what would you like to talk about anyway now?
About Aburasoba!
What do you want to eat now?
Abura soba!
What is your current goal as KANAMI Ishiguri?
Yes, I want to do my best to be a leader of the Hello Project as well as of Ocha-no-Ma.
Thank you very much!
Your last question was really cool, wasn't it?
Thank you very much.
Tea ceremony horseYes, you are always leading me and I hope you will continue to do so.
I'll do my best.
I'd like to delve deeper into what I'm interested in now.
Okay.
What do you want to talk about?
Yes.
Oil Soba Noodles
And what you want to eat?
Abura soba!
That's why I love abura soba so much.
But I tell the members every morning.
I tell the members that I had abura soba last night too.
There was a time when I ate it every day for a week.
Sometimes I ate it three times a day.
I love it so much!
So I hope to spread this love of abura soba around the world.
Yes, I really do... because I say I eat it every day.
Please understand my love for abura soba!
And the thing I wanted to express most in the new single "Chihaya Productions" is roughness.
Yes, sir.
Yes, this song "Chihaya Blue" has a very rough dance performance.
I think the song "Chihaya Blue" has the meaning of rough and rugged, and I really like the performance that can be done by 10 members.
I like the performance that can be done only by 10 dancers coming together, and I often stand in the middle of the song so that I can make the song "Chihaya Blue" more exciting.
I tried my best to express the song "Chihaya Blue" more.
Hallo! Stay tuned for more after this!
I'm Chihiro Miyakoshi, a 13-year-old junior high school student from Tokyo.
When I was in the third grade of elementary school, I went to see "Akage no Iori" starring Reina Tanaka.
She sang very well and was very cute, so I admired her a lot!
The fantasy of Morning Musume。 Morning Musume's fantasy is about to begin!
I love that Michishige-san and Rena Tanaka-san are so cute and mature.
To see the movie!
Thank you for your hard work!
I like "Doctor X" and "The Great Hospital Election." My mom recommended it to me and I was a little curious about it, so I watched it for the first time and found it really interesting.
I'm good at dancing, jazz funk, etc. I like curry rice, hamburgers and sushi rice.
I play basketball and dodgeball.
I have a cat.
I have a cat now.
Her name is Mikeco.
When he runs out of food
When he runs out of food, he sometimes asks for more food.
His behavior is very cute.
Math and arithmetic.
He can speak using only vowels.
When I was in elementary school.
I was supposed to speak using only vowels.
I would introduce myself.
I could do it in one shot.
I thought I was good at it.
Surprisingly, I'm often called strange
I'm often called a natural.
From the new school year
I'm a quiet person.
Surprisingly quiet
But when he talks
But when she talks, she's surprisingly loud.
Once you get to know her...
I'm sure we'll talk a lot.
I'm sure we'll have a lot to talk about.
Bug spray.
When I was little.
I wasn't so much of a normal person.
I was quiet.
I hate bugs these days. I always take it with me when I go to the mountains.
I guess it's because mosquito bites are so itchy.
I'm going to do a turn.
My bangs are getting longer before I know it.
I'm not very good at singing, so I'd like to improve my singing.
I want to do my best in self-study every day so that I can get the high notes and rhythm right.
I also want to try new genres of dance that I haven't tried before.
I want to be able to dance in various genres in a cool way.
When the cold wind rustled softly
I suddenly felt lonely and my heart was in pain
Ah, please notice me
This time, Chihiro Miyakoshi was the guest of the Hallo Pro trainee corner.
She was wonderful!
She's so cute. Do you have any connection with her?
I haven't seen Miyakoshi and the other trainees since they joined the show.
I haven't had the chance to talk to Miyakoshi and the other trainees in depth.
I haven't had a chance to talk to her in depth.
But we would pass by each other at Hello Project concerts and she would greet me with a smile.
She greeted me with a smile.
She greeted me with a smile and seemed mature
I have an image of her.
I have an image of her as a mature girl when she starts to perform.
I've also seen the video of her performance test and a little bit of her talk at the Hello Project concert.
I've talked with her a little bit at Hello Project concerts.
Chihiro is very attractive when she is moving.
I mean, she's the type of girl who makes me fall in love with her when our eyes meet.
I couldn't really look her in the eye and talk to her.
I couldn't really look her in the eye, but I thought she was really cute.
Yes, we are also long-time trainee members of Halo Pro.
When you look back on your time as a trainee, is there anything that stands out in your mind?
Well, when we first started as a trainee, we were very young...
Yes.
I could only see the future, and I felt like I was shining.
I was happy to go to school every day and I was determined to do my best.
But as the years went by, I started to feel anxious.
I've been battling with anxiety about when I'll make my debut and when I won't.
I think I'm going to have to fight the anxiety of wondering when I'll be able to debut or not.
But after I joined the Halo Pro Trainee Unit
I started to feel that way.
The members and teachers around me supported me.
When I was in trouble, there were so many children who would come to me for advice.
I think it was a time when I realized how big it was.
How did I feel when I was a trainee?
When I was a trainee, I was so innocent and energetic that I was determined to do my best.
But as I grew up, I absorbed various feelings and emotions.
As I grew up, I absorbed various feelings and emotions.
There were times when I wanted to focus on other things besides idol activities.
I'm sure we all have those times.
So during those times...
I still wanted to work with these girls.
I'm glad.
When we were a trainee unit.
There was a time when I thought about quitting the trainee unit.
But if I did, I wouldn't be able to see
I thought that if I quit, I wouldn't be able to see the members of the trainee unit that I have now.
I thought that I would not be able to meet the members of the trainee unit if I ended my activities, and I wanted to continue working with them.
Please look forward to the next installment of Halo Pro Trainees Corner.
Haloste, Kanami Ishiguri and Nanami Kubota from Ochanoma will be introducing the movement of Hello Project for the next one week.
This time, we'll be introducing the next week of Hello Project.
This time, we'll be showing you our schedule for the week of September 12th to 18th.
There's a lot happening on the 12th, lots of events, and yes, lots of opportunities to see you all.
We're very happy to have you here.
We have a lot of events and tours in the fall, but we as tea horses are really moving forward.
As you can see from the sound chart here...
If you look at this chart, you'll see that we always have a chance to see you every day.
If you are in the neighborhood, I would like you to come and see us.
Yes, we have already held the release events for the 4th single at several places.
I, Kubota, am going to have a release event at McHarry Shin Toshin in Chiba prefecture and at Ill Mall McHarry Shin Toshin.
Kubota is from Chiba prefecture.
Kubota is from Chiba prefecture, so it was like a triumphant return to Japan.
I'm from Chiba prefecture, so it was like a triumphant return to Japan for the release event, and a lot of people came.
I was so happy that everyone said "Welcome back Kubota, I've been looking forward to this event".
I've had the opportunity to perform at Ill Mall Makuhari Shin Toshin in Chiba for my previous singles, so I'd like to do my best so that I can do it again.
I would like to do my best so that I can go there again.
Many of the release events are held in open spaces.
There are many people who come to our events, not only those who say they like Ocha-no-Ma, but also those who come to our events.
I'm very happy to have the opportunity to do so.
I think it's a great opportunity for us.
And I think it's a great opportunity for me to meet people who have come to see me now.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who came to see us now.
I would like to cherish each of these encounters and continue to do my best at these events.
I will also be performing at the At Jam Expo 2024.
This is an event that I have performed at many times since I was a member of the Hello Project trainee unit.
There will be many other Hello Project groups performing as well, so I hope you will come and enjoy the show.
I hope you can come and join us!
If you can make it, please come and spend some time with Hello Project!
We look forward to seeing you there!
We are looking forward to seeing you!
We look forward to seeing you soon!
We look forward to meeting you
We are looking forward to seeing you soon!
SBIKE FACTORY's Summer Festival 2024 Scorching Heat is over.
How was it?
Yes, it was great. There are things that can only be done in the scorching heat.
For example, the Japanese drums and Bon Odori dance that I performed, and the way the audience danced was very cute.
Ha-ha-ha.
You sang solo with Funa-chan, didn't you?
Yes. And I also sang a solo.
It was scorching hot.
We have a shuffle every year, so I've done the trio and Rio.
I did a solo today, and it's getting fewer and fewer.
So I would like to do it again next year,
What will happen?
It was fun.
I was really nervous until just before the show.
I was really nervous until just before the show, but the moment I got on stage, I was so happy and the penlights were so beautiful.
It was raining this year.
But I was so happy that I couldn't even think about the rain.
I had so much fun!
It was so much fun in a good way.
And so many fans came to support us.
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much.
And now we, Tsubaki Factory, are going to start Tsubaki Factory Live Tour 2024 Autumn Pulse on September 8th!
Yes, this is the first live house tour not from me, but from my peers, and I'm very nervous, but I want to enjoy it,
I think the strength of a tour caption is that we have songs that match the four seasons, so I hope we can make it an autumn-like tour.
Yes, I, Miu Ishii, have an image of a live house that is quite close to everyone.
I have an image of a live house where I am very close to everyone.
I would like to do my best so that you can feel my heartbeat as the title says.
I will do my best with all my might.
Let's do our best!
So please come to the fall tour too!
Wow!
That's all.
This is Spike Factory!
Kanami Ishigiri from Ocha-no-Ma
and Nanami Kubota from Ocha-no-Ma, Halo! stay, brought to you by Kanami Ishigiri and Nanami Kubota of Tea Horse!
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Well, Kanami Ishigiri and I usually talk together and we've become very close members.
So we are very close to each other and we usually talk together. It's the first time for me to MC a show like this with her, so it's a little fresh.
It's rare for me to speak in such a proper way.
I was quite nervous.
Yes, but it went pretty smoothly and I think it went well.
I hope you had a good time at EMC.
It was a very enjoyable time.
Here's an announcement!
New single "Chihayaburu Tomodachi Tento Zu" was released today!
We will have a mini-live & farewell party in Hyogo on 12th, Aichi on 13th and Kanagawa on 17th.
Please come and see us at Ochanoma!
And Ochanoma Live Tour 2024 Season 2: Our hometown is Japan!
We will be performing in Wakayama this weekend, so please look forward to it! On September 14, we will be performing with Rosie Chronicle at At Jam Expo 2024 supported by upt!
Please come and see our performance!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
We were joined by Kanami Ishikiri and Nanami Kubota of Ocha-no-Mama!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!